sentence,labels
Alice moved to Bangalore after leaving Microsoft,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Microsoft was founded by Bob in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to London after leaving Apple,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Bob moved to London after leaving Apple,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Apple was founded by Bob in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to Amazon in New York New York,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
Bob joined Apple in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in London,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Amazon was founded by Alice in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
John left OpenAI in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob left Google in London,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to Paris after leaving Amazon,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Google was founded by John in London,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to Google in New York New York,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Samantha in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Samantha in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob moved to Bangalore after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Microsoft was founded by John in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
John works at OpenAI in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs works at OpenAI in London,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to Tokyo after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Apple was founded by Alice in New York New York,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to New York New York after leaving Microsoft,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs joined Google in London,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Alice in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to Bangalore after leaving Amazon,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Alice joined Google in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to New York New York after leaving Microsoft,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Alice moved to Microsoft in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Alice moved to New York New York after leaving Google,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
John joined Google in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to Microsoft in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha left Apple in New York New York,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
John left Microsoft in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by John in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in New York New York,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
Alice moved to New York New York after leaving Apple,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
John founded OpenAI in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs founded Amazon in London,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to London after leaving Microsoft,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Alice moved to Amazon in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob moved to London after leaving Amazon,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Samantha moved to Paris after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Alice joined Google in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
OpenAI was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in New York New York,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
Alice joined Amazon in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Alice moved to Paris after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
OpenAI was founded by Bob in New York New York,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs founded Apple in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Amazon was founded by John in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Amazon was founded by Samantha in London,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob moved to Bangalore after leaving Google,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
OpenAI was founded by Samantha in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Apple was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs founded Apple in New York New York,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
OpenAI was founded by Samantha in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
John moved to Paris after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Samantha moved to Tokyo after leaving Microsoft,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
John joined Amazon in London,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob joined Microsoft in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
OpenAI was founded by Samantha in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs founded Apple in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Google was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
OpenAI was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in London,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha joined Amazon in London,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob founded OpenAI in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to London after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Google was founded by Samantha in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by Samantha in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Alice left Amazon in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
John moved to Paris after leaving Google,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Samantha moved to Google in London,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to New York New York after leaving Amazon,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Google was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to New York New York after leaving Google,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Bob moved to Bangalore after leaving Amazon,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Google was founded by Alice in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Google was founded by Bob in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Samantha moved to Microsoft in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob moved to Paris after leaving Microsoft,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Amazon was founded by Samantha in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
OpenAI was founded by Bob in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob joined OpenAI in London,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Apple was founded by John in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Microsoft was founded by John in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Apple was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob moved to London after leaving Google,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Alice moved to OpenAI in Paris,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs moved to Paris after leaving Google,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Bob moved to London after leaving OpenAI,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Google was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Tokyo,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Amazon was founded by John in Paris,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Google was founded by Steve Jobs Steve Jobs in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Bob moved to Bangalore after leaving Apple,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG']"
Bob joined Amazon in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Steve Jobs Steve Jobs founded Apple in Bangalore,"['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Amazon was founded by Bob in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Alice moved to Google in Tokyo,"['B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-ORG', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
Google was founded by John in Bangalore,"['B-ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-LOC']"
